{
  "BookName": "Starter Toeic",
  "Units": [
    {
      "Unit": 1,
      "Part2": {
        "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1DmG8mQ28-oLl-6iKuitj_nbxM573HqSh/view?usp=drive_link",
        "Quiz": [
          {
            "Question": "I have a headache. Do we have any aspirin?",
            "Answers": [
              "Look in the medicine cabinet in the bathroom.",
              "She is on her way home.",
              "I feel fine."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Look in the medicine cabinet in the bathroom."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Can I make a doctor’s appointment for Monday, please?",
            "Answers": [
              "Monday is a weekday.",
              "Give the children some candy.",
              "Yes. Is 2:30 OK?"
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Yes. Is 2:30 OK?"
          },
          {
            "Question": "Do you have to study hard to become a dentist?",
            "Answers": [
              "Yes. It is a lot of work.",
              "The dentist's office is next to the barber shop.",
              "She will return tomorrow afternoon."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Yes. It is a lot of work."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Can you recommend a good eye doctor?",
            "Answers": [
              "I wear glasses.",
              "Yes. I go to Doctor Park.",
              "Don’t worry so much. You’ll be fine."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Yes. I go to Doctor Park."
          },
          {
            "Question": "She cut her finger! What should we do?",
            "Answers": [
              "There are six students in the class.",
              "I’d like a drink of water.",
              "It’s not too deep. Cover it with a small bandage."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "It’s not too deep. Cover it with a small bandage."
          }
        ]
      },
      "Part3": {
          "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1zZjEkDyhA3cFTDOaudlIG7iZiqtvhsIV/view?usp=drive_link"
      },
      "Part4": {
          "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1_bwhgZYNofIBfO4jK5fI2vWBQd2E7t2O/view?usp=drive_link"
      }
    },
    {
      "Unit": 2,
      "Part2": {
        "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1XeOG95IPJzuO3VHCjFv-A9rZC4fpLX4s/view?usp=drive_link",
        "Quiz": [
          {
            "Question": "I'm so happy! I got an A in History!",
            "Answers": [
              "He is in the classroom right now.",
              "Congratulations!",
              "My history teacher's name is Mrs. Lewis."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Congratulations!"
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which class do you have on Tuesday mornings?",
            "Answers": [
              "French.",
              "I don’t like to wake up early.",
              "We can go together."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "French."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Will Brian go to university next year?",
            "Answers": [
              "Brian studies hard.",
              "She gave him the letter.",
              "No. He still has one more year of high school."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "No. He still has one more year of high school."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Is Professor Green your music teacher?",
            "Answers": [
              "Green is my favorite color.",
              "No, Mrs. Benson is.",
              "The music store is closed today."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "No, Mrs. Benson is."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Can you take these books back to the library for me?",
            "Answers": [
              "There is some extra paper in the desk drawer.",
              "The books are expensive.",
              "Yes, I'll put them in my bag."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Yes, I'll put them in my bag."
          }
        ]
      },
      "Part3": {
          "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1-dkV_-SeHeMsdsP1WShaHBkrYAjPgrGZ/view?usp=drive_link"
      },
      "Part4": {
          "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1vGmdwJrg52102XVbs249verzr0mSaM0_/view?usp=drive_link"
      }
    },
    {
      "Unit": 3,
      "Part2": {
        "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1JsZlg4CmlACL5fQ6TaK22VE7qq4s5Zij/view?usp=drive_link",
        "Quiz": [
          {
            "Question": "Why didn’t you answer the phone last night?",
            "Answers": [
              "I was taking a bath when it rang.",
              "It was hot last night.",
              "That’s a good idea."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "I was taking a bath when it rang."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Whose turn is it to wash the dishes?",
            "Answers": [
              "I want to eat pizza.",
              "I think it’s my turn.",
              "Turn over."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "I think it’s my turn."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Did you mow the grass this morning?",
            "Answers": [
              "Yes, it looks great, doesn’t it?",
              "It rained this morning.",
              "No, I’m busy."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Yes, it looks great, doesn’t it?"
          },
          {
            "Question": "Where are your brothers?",
            "Answers": [
              "They are my brothers.",
              "I am at home.",
              "They’re in the garden, Mom."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "They’re in the garden, Mom."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Have you finished the laundry yet?",
            "Answers": [
              "No, the washing machine is broken.",
              "He is a dry cleaner.",
              "I like to do laundry."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "No, the washing machine is broken."
          }
        ]
      },
      "Part3": {
          "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1uzYS9_IZz3-AMNu7HbSjxtkuLvOImeR4/view?usp=drive_link"
      },
      "Part4": {
          "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1V08lgMXq8kPjXb-IfiK4N38ZJ2fv8zGF/view?usp=drive_link"
      }
    },
    {
      "Unit": 4,
      "Part2": {
        "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1drwqzoCRSAmWA49awaUfjEL4dTvPSsSa/view?usp=drive_link",
        "Quiz": [
          {
            "Question": "What time does the movie start?",
            "Answers": [
              "I think it starts at 3:30.",
              "Yes, let’s go to see a movie.",
              "There are three movie theaters."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "I think it starts at 3:30."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Is there anything good on TV tonight?",
            "Answers": [
              "Did you buy it?",
              "No, just the usual.",
              "There's a book on the TV."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "No, just the usual."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Have you seen the new musical at the Play House?",
            "Answers": [
              "Yes, it was great.",
              "Yes, it is the Play House.",
              "I like musicals."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Yes, it was great."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Where is my movie ticket?",
            "Answers": [
              "It's already 4 o'clock.",
              "This is a good movie.",
              "There it is, under that chair."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "There it is, under that chair."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Do you like watching comedies?",
            "Answers": [
              "No, I prefer action movies.",
              "It is not a comedy.",
              "This is very funny."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "This is very funny."
          }
        ]
      },
      "Part3": {
          "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1cW-5L2LUoAwWUISwHDL1w8hywdbl3J6w/view?usp=drive_link"
      },
      "Part4": {
          "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/12u324GmktqqzQL5QpgFBs-zh0BIrOoPP/view?usp=drive_link"
      }
    },
    {
      "Unit": 5,
      "Part2": {
        "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1udjgcfNU-aWMG33Uf7vOl6_Bc485Xl35/view?usp=drive_link",
        "Quiz": [
          {
            "Question": "Where do you work?",
            "Answers": [
              "At 9:00 a.m., usually.",
              "He went on vacation.",
              "In the office building on the corner."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "In the office building on the corner."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Can you help me file these papers?",
            "Answers": [
              "I don’t know how to type.",
              "Sure. Let's do it together.",
              "My desk is in the corner."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Sure. Let's do it together."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Did the boss hire a new worker?",
            "Answers": [
              "Yes, her name is Sue.",
              "I went to New York once.",
              "His office is down the hall."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Yes, her name is Sue."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Will you come to work on Saturday?",
            "Answers": [
              "The coffee has sugar in it.",
              "I like my job.",
              "No, I finished everything today."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "No, I finished everything today."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Have you ever worked in a grocery store?",
            "Answers": [
              "They sell fruits and vegetables.",
              "Yes, when I was in university.",
              "I can't go with you."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Yes, when I was in university."
          }
        ]
      },
      "Part3": {
          "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1l-9_rzR6b3TZLEnZbKub8zYBzxTjKgtI/view?usp=drive_link"
      },
      "Part4": {
          "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1KoGkGvM1YPyZgCz7UCdv062NuI4Ag3iJ/view?usp=drive_link"
      }
    },
    {
      "Unit": 6,
      "Part2": {
        "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1dmp6gtVINyuy5aKlIvTyxdumL-N2XAPx/view?usp=drive_link",
        "Quiz": [
          {
            "Question": "Where did you go on vacation?",
            "Answers": [
              "Yes, the weather was terrible.",
              "We went to Spain for a week.",
              "Yes, we went on vacation."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "We went to Spain for a week."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Do you prefer the seaside or the mountains?",
            "Answers": [
              "Well, I like the beach more than the mountains.",
              "I went to the seaside two years ago.",
              "I prefer them both."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Well, I like the beach more than the mountains."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Are there a lot of interesting museums in Paris?",
            "Answers": [
              "No, it is less expensive.",
              "Yes, there are hundreds.",
              "I like museums."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Yes, there are hundreds."
          },
          {
            "Question": "How was your flight?",
            "Answers": [
              "It was just awful.",
              "I woke up late today.",
              "Yes, it was."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "It was just awful."
          },
          {
            "Question": "When is Jane coming back?",
            "Answers": [
              "Oh, she came back this morning.",
              "She is coming.",
              "Jane didn’t come back."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Oh, she came back this morning."
          }
        ]
      },
      "Part3": {
          "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Pn37eGr3_lP65bQhl6_jD0wWWrgVCh8_/view?usp=drive_link"
      },
      "Part4": {
          "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1n48VPpaoZcwO_tI87Sd_D2SNZLEcDGEn/view?usp=drive_link"
      }
    },
    {
      "Unit": 7,
      "Part2": {
        "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1-4plAAXwoij5rTPOkpZ5PO2CcHyI-PsQ/view?usp=drive_link",
        "Quiz": [
          {
            "Question": "Where is the art museum?",
            "Answers": [
              "Down the street, next to the post office.",
              "Not today. I'm busy.",
              "Last week."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Down the street, next to the post office."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Can you paint very well?",
            "Answers": [
              "My favorite color is blue.",
              "Yes, I took lessons for five years.",
              "He is not home right now."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Yes, I took lessons for five years."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Did you buy some new paint brushes?",
            "Answers": [
              "I have no money.",
              "They went to the park.",
              "Yes, six of them."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Yes, six of them."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Does she use a computer to color her drawings?",
            "Answers": [
              "No, she paints them all by hand.",
              "She loves computer programming.",
              "Yes, she has a computer."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "No, she paints them all by hand."
          },
          {
            "Question": "When will he have his art exhibit?",
            "Answers": [
              "At the museum.",
              "I don’t go there often.",
              "Next Saturday."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Next Saturday."
          }
        ]
      },
      "Part3": {
          "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1pjjmmomRg_EfeZQ1F4nNTCkCf_-94t6z/view?usp=drive_link"
      },
      "Part4": {
          "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/149607IqOY1pxhBhypMLncv1XplcqPe5g/view?usp=drive_link"
      }
    },
    {
      "Unit": 8,
      "Part2": {
        "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1AWZUVXL2qsFbKziwsIi7cPYJTCaYHwgT/view?usp=drive_link",
        "Quiz": [
          {
            "Question": "How often do you listen to the radio?",
            "Answers": [
              "I usually listen every morning.",
              "It is not a radio.",
              "Yes, I like listening to the radio."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "I usually listen every morning."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Are you going to the concert tonight?",
            "Answers": [
              "He is a rock musician.",
              "No, I couldn’t get a ticket.",
              "I often go to concerts."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "No, I couldn’t get a ticket."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Where did you buy this album?",
            "Answers": [
              "I didn’t. I downloaded these songs for free.",
              "I often buy new albums.",
              "I have about twenty albums."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "I didn’t. I downloaded these songs for free."
          },
          {
            "Question": "What is your favorite kind of music?",
            "Answers": [
              "I like everything except jazz.",
              "It is my favorite kind of music.",
              "I like listening to music."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "I like everything except jazz."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Have you ever been to the opera?",
            "Answers": [
              "My mother taught me.",
              "I have been just once.",
              "I didn’t go last year."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "I have been just once."
          }
        ]
      },
      "Part3": {
          "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1bv7gHehFcqUWiS9-c5FRD6jYPz9N7HGY/view?usp=drive_link"
      },
      "Part4": {
          "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1co6OyNZefcROJoGopmr7y6gWvotN3MvW/view?usp=drive_link"
      }
    },
    {
      "Unit": 9,
      "Part2": {
        "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1EY_0_wD4_sjEDyq3tmjTT81MfmkxBsLu/view?usp=drive_link",
        "Quiz": [
          {
            "Question": "I have two tickets to the baseball game. Would you like to go with me?",
            "Answers": [
              "I don’t have a baseball.",
              "Yes, I'd love to!",
              "He went yesterday."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Yes, I'd love to!"
          },
          {
            "Question": "Does anyone here know how to ski?",
            "Answers": [
              "I do, a little.",
              "He will be here soon.",
              "It's five o'clock."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "I do, a little."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Where are they going to build the new sports stadium?",
            "Answers": [
              "It will be full of people.",
              "I've never gone there before.",
              "Near the university."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Near the university."
          },
          {
            "Question": "How did you injure your leg?",
            "Answers": [
              "Playing soccer.",
              "It doesn’t hurt too much.",
              "It’s my left leg."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Playing soccer."
          },
          {
            "Question": "I'm too short to play basketball.",
            "Answers": [
              "I have a basketball, too.",
              "No, you're not. Give it a try!",
              "Shorts are for summer."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "No, you're not. Give it a try!"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Part3": {
          "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1R5gYLzYdSPbwhA1APSXs4VoLe37lwp29/view?usp=drive_link"
      },
      "Part4": {
          "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1UcEwfowFo40wtj6OLpFHGz5wf6kLO44r/view?usp=drive_link"
      }
    },
    {
      "Unit": 10,
      "Part2": {
        "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1glS9d3K_l7cS7LLrpTWRzuMyNEPr9TgJ/view?usp=drive_link",
        "Quiz": [
          {
            "Question": "Are you hungry?",
            "Answers": [
              "I eat breakfast every day.",
              "Yes, let's eat something.",
              "Yes, I already ate, thank you."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Yes, I already ate, thank you."
          },
          {
            "Question": "What is in your sandwich?",
            "Answers": [
              "Cheese and tomato.",
              "This is my sandwich.",
              "I often eat sandwiches."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Cheese and tomato."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Do you eat meat?",
            "Answers": [
              "No, I'm a vegetarian.",
              "Beef and pork are meats.",
              "No, I don't have any meat."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "No, I'm a vegetarian."
          },
          {
            "Question": "How was that new restaurant?",
            "Answers": [
              "I never eat in restaurants.",
              "The food was OK, but the service was poor.",
              "It's an Italian restaurant."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "The food was OK, but the service was poor."
          },
          {
            "Question": "What time is dinner?",
            "Answers": [
              "Let's have dinner tomorrow.",
              "It's dinner time.",
              "It's at seven."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "It's at seven."
          }
        ]
      },
      "Part3": {
          "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1jXaYHpZVwQWOCHO7XNSZF7Ahmu79IVKv/view?usp=drive_link"
      },
      "Part4": {
          "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1vUlqquj1MidzbpmwkGx1rBnInvxv9U32/view?usp=drive_link"
      }
    },
    {
      "Unit": 11,
      "Part2": {
        "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1izK53bgOrrJiruTa2Ioq9UUTXrNyG8px/view?usp=drive_link",
        "Quiz": [
          {
            "Question": "Have you seen my calculator? I can't find it anywhere!",
            "Answers": [
              "It's on your desk.",
              "Thank you very much.",
              "That's great news."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "It's on your desk."
          },
          {
            "Question": "This fish is very strange-looking. What is it?",
            "Answers": [
              "It's a fish.",
              "Don't look at it.",
              "It's a puffer fish."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "It's a puffer fish."
          },
          {
            "Question": "What is the name of the planet closest to Earth?",
            "Answers": [
              "It's Mars.",
              "My name is Jimmy.",
              "That's right."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "It's Mars."
          },
          {
            "Question": "How do you know so much about chemicals?",
            "Answers": [
              "I studied history.",
              "I studied chemistry.",
              "I studied English."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "I studied chemistry."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Can I borrow your telescope tomorrow night?",
            "Answers": [
              "I have two televisions.",
              "Sure. It's in my bedroom.",
              "No thanks, I'm busy."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Sure. It's in my bedroom."
          }
        ]
      },
      "Part3": {
          "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/194aXvOS6XKErMsHZs3YNcbZx4QWU1qtE/view?usp=drive_link"
      },
      "Part4": {
          "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1WU2M2wlNSq8Ir3eBhZFH9yqaSEjvdtJ4/view?usp=drive_link"
      }
    },
    {
      "Unit": 12,
      "Part2": {
        "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1u_iShm0VNX6mxqZG-_xeERzSbkmGSIDR/view?usp=drive_link",
        "Quiz": [
          {
            "Question": "Do you still collect stamps?",
            "Answers": [
              "Yes, I have about 2,000 now.",
              "Yes, these are stamps.",
              "No, she didn’t stamp it."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "Yes, I have about 2,000 now."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Is the art gallery open today?",
            "Answers": [
              "No, it’s closed until next week.",
              "I went to the gallery once.",
              "It usually opens at 9 a.m."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "No, it’s closed until next week."
          },
          {
            "Question": "How long have you been learning the piano?",
            "Answers": [
              "For about 5 years.",
              "Every Monday.",
              "It takes about an hour."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "For about 5 years."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Do you want to go swimming this weekend?",
            "Answers": [
              "The swimming pool is near my house.",
              "I often go swimming.",
              "No, thanks. I have other plans."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "No, thanks. I have other plans."
          },
          {
            "Question": "What's your hobby?",
            "Answers": [
              "I paint watercolor pictures.",
              "My mother likes to knit.",
              "It’s not my hobby."
            ],
            "CorrectAnswer": "I paint watercolor pictures."
          }
        ]
      },
      "Part3": {
          "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1_tsT06wCirX6FuIcTVywNW7V_E9losq-/view?usp=drive_link"
      },
      "Part4": {
          "Src": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1WeqwKEe-Ny_hxyPr17_VUFhbZRAAjIG1/view?usp=drive_link"
      }
    }
  ],
  "Test": {
    "Src2": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1XPBKjHMIHcdNkap4GZQSv3IqKUBFJaN6/view?usp=drive_link",
    "Src3": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1t470IAr1LeKJFoIN9nBTQUgDaPt0Hk7n/view?usp=drive_link",
    "Src4": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1a9yHvx8Z4ziJ4L6Eh9cakNfTJ_gAxhUe/view?usp=drive_link",
    "Quiz": [
      {
        "Question": "Did you get up early this morning?",
        "Answers": [
          "I went to bed last night.",
          "No, I got up late.",
          "Yes, I had breakfast."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "No, I got up late."
      },
      {
        "Question": "How is your father?",
        "Answers": [
          "He's 65 years old.",
          "Yes, he is.",
          "Not bad at all."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "Not bad at all."
      },
      {
        "Question": "What's new?",
        "Answers": [
          "Nothing special.",
          "I'm new here.",
          "Fine, thanks."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "Fine, thanks."
      },
      {
        "Question": "How have you been lately?",
        "Answers": [
          "Pretty busy.",
          "I got up late.",
          "By subway."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "Pretty busy."
      },
      {
        "Question": "Did you call me yesterday?",
        "Answers": [
          "Yes, I do.",
          "Yes, I wanted to speak to you.",
          "No, I wasn't there."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "Yes, I wanted to speak to you."
      },
      {
        "Question": "What time does the meeting start?",
        "Answers": [
          "It starts just fine.",
          "In just a few minutes.",
          "Yes, I'll be at the meeting."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "In just a few minutes."
      },
      {
        "Question": "Did you go to the bank?",
        "Answers": [
          "Sorry, I didn't mean to.",
          "Yes, you can.",
          "It's closed today."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "It's closed today."
      },
      {
        "Question": "Where would you like to go for lunch?",
        "Answers": [
          "No, thanks. I've had enough.",
          "It doesn’t matter.",
          "Yes, I'm going."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "Yes, I'm going."
      },
      {
        "Question": "Have you read The Minister's Son?",
        "Answers": [
          "No, but I've heard it's very good.",
          "Of course you can borrow it.",
          "I don't know him."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "No, but I've heard it's very good."
      },
      {
        "Question": "How do you start the washing machine?",
        "Answers": [
          "They're very expensive.",
          "I don’t have a washing machine.",
          "Just wait, and I'll do it for you."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "Just wait, and I'll do it for you."
      },
      {
        "Question": "Can you come over after the show?",
        "Answers": [
          "I'd love to go to the show!",
          "That would be nice.",
          "Yes, I did."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "That would be nice."
      },
      {
        "Question": "Are you finished with that magazine?",
        "Answers": [
          "Just about.",
          "That will be $1.25, please.",
          "Yes, I get it every month."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "Just about."
      },
      {
        "Question": "Is the cat sick?",
        "Answers": [
          "I don't have six cats.",
          "No, it's just sleeping.",
          "Yes, I agree."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "No, it's just sleeping."
      },
      {
        "Question": "Why did she cancel the trip?",
        "Answers": [
          "She loves to fly.",
          "No, she didn't.",
          "She has the flu."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "She has the flu."
      },
      {
        "Question": "When is the next train?",
        "Answers": [
          "5 o'clock.",
          "Over there.",
          "It's going to Chicago."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "5 o'clock."
      },
      {
        "Question": "Did your sister have her baby?",
        "Answers": [
          "Yes, she does.",
          "Not yet.",
          "She was a cute baby."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "Not yet."
      },
      {
        "Question": "How long does the program last?",
        "Answers": [
          "No, it will be first.",
          "It's only an hour long.",
          "The program starts in 5 minutes."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "It's only an hour long."
      },
      {
        "Question": "Where does it hurt?",
        "Answers": [
          "Yes, very much.",
          "I don't think so.",
          "Above my knee."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "Above my knee."
      },
      {
        "Question": "Is this table OK for you?",
        "Answers": [
          "It's perfect.",
          "Yes, it's for me.",
          "That will be all."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "It's perfect."
      },
      {
        "Question": "Which bag is yours?",
        "Answers": [
          "No, it isn't.",
          "That one.",
          "I like this bag."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "That one."
      },
      {
        "Question": "Who was absent from class today?",
        "Answers": [
          "They went out after class.",
          "I sent them to class.",
          "Only one student."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "Only one student."
      },
      {
        "Question": "Do you still have that coffee maker?",
        "Answers": [
          "Sure, anytime.",
          "No, I sold it.",
          "No, thanks. I don't drink coffee."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "No, I sold it."
      },
      {
        "Question": "How often do you go out to eat?",
        "Answers": [
          "Great! I'll pick you up at 7:00.",
          "Last Friday night.",
          "Every weekend."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "Every weekend."
      },
      {
        "Question": "Can you tell me where the bus stop is?",
        "Answers": [
          "I appreciate your help.",
          "Sorry, I'm from out of town.",
          "The next stop is Central Park."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "The next stop is Central Park."
      },
      {
        "Question": "What are the kids doing?",
        "Answers": [
          "They are doing well, thank you.",
          "I don't know. I think I'll go check on them.",
          "Yes, they did it."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "I don't know. I think I'll go check on them."
      },
      {
        "Question": "Is the copy machine still broken?",
        "Answers": [
          "No, it was fixed this morning.",
          "Yes, I'll make some copies.",
          "Please take a break."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "No, it was fixed this morning."
      },
      {
        "Question": "Why is the house so quiet?",
        "Answers": [
          "OK. I'll be quiet.",
          "Nobody is home.",
          "In the afternoons."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "Nobody is home."
      },
      {
        "Question": "When are you going to the therapist?",
        "Answers": [
          "I am feeling better, thanks.",
          "He said there was no problem.",
          "Tomorrow morning."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "Tomorrow morning."
      },
      {
        "Question": "Would you go outside to smoke?",
        "Answers": [
          "Yes, I can see the smoke.",
          "Of course.",
          "Usually after dinner."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "Usually after dinner."
      },
      {
        "Question": "Do you have to go so soon?",
        "Answers": [
          "I'm afraid so.",
          "Yes, you should.",
          "I left as soon as I could."
        ],
        "CorrectAnswer": "I'm afraid so."
      }
    ]
  }
}